ancientfaces.com 2019-12-10

# Your Privacy is Important | AncientFaces Privacy Policy

AncientFaces knows that you care about the information you share. We appreciate and value your trust. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat your information. By visiting AncientFaces you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy 

**Last Updated on May 25, 2018**. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for users that sign up for AncientFaces accounts on or after May 25, 2018 and will become effective on May 25, 2018 for users that already have AncientFaces accounts. This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our services, including those offered through our websites, and emails (collectively, the "Service"). The terms "we", "us", and “AncientFaces" refer to AncientFaces LLC., a California Limited Liability Company with its headquarters in San Jose, California. When you use the Service, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## TABLE OF CONTENTS

  1. Information We Collect and How We Use It
  2. Cookies
  3. Third Parties
  4. Controlling Your Personal Data
  5. Data Retention and Account Termination
  6. Children
  7. Security
  8. Contact Information
  9. Modifications to This Privacy Policy
  10. California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

### 1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

We may collect and store information about you in connection with your use of the Service, including any information you transmit to or through the Service. We use that information to provide the Service’s functionality, fulfill your requests, improve the Service’s quality, engage in research and analysis relating to the Service, personalize your experience, track usage of the Service, display relevant advertising, market the Service, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems, allow for disaster recovery, enhance the security of the Service, and comply with legal obligations. Even when we do not retain such information, it still must be transmitted to our servers initially and stored long enough to process. Please also note: 

  1. Account Information: If you create a AncientFaces account, we may store and use the information you provide during that process, such as your full name, email address, and other information you may provide with your account, such as your gender and birth date. We may publicly display your first and last name, as well as any photo or other content you submit through the registration process, as part of your account profile. You can modify some of the information associated with your account through your account settings. If you believe that someone has created an unauthorized account depicting you or your likeness, you can request its removal by contacting us. 
  2. Public Content: Your contributions to the Service are intended for public consumption and are therefore viewable by the public, including your photos, biographies, comments, favorites, and edits to pages listed on AncientFaces. Your account profile (e.g., first name, last name, month joined, profile photos, favorites, uploads and friends) is also intended for public consumption, as is some of your other activity through the Service, such as how you favorite other people’s contributions, what biographies and photos you upload, which users, biographies, surnames and photos you follow. You can limit the public nature of some of these activities through your account settings. 
  3. Contacts: You can invite others to join AncientFaces by providing us with their contact information or by allowing us to access your contacts from your computer, mobile device, or third party sites to select which individuals you want to invite. If you allow us to access your contacts, we may transmit that information to our servers long enough to process your invitations. 
  4. Communications: When you sign up for an account or use certain features, you are opting to receive messages from other users, businesses, and AncientFaces. You can manage some of your messaging preferences through your account settings, but note that you cannot opt out of receiving certain administrative, transactional, or legal messages from AncientFaces. For example, if you upload photos or create biographies through the Service, we may send you messages about your transaction using the contact information you provide. We may also track your actions in response to the messages you receive from us or through the Service, such as whether you deleted, opened, or forwarded such messages. If you exchange messages with others through the Service, we may store them in order to process and deliver them or allow you to manage them, and we may review and disclose them in connection with investigations related to use of the Service, as well as our efforts to improve the Service. We may not deliver messages that we believe are objectionable, such as spam messages or fraudulent solicitations. We may also store information that you provide through communications to us, including from phone calls, letters, emails and other electronic messages or in person. 
  5. Activity: We may store information about your use of the Service, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit and uploads you make through the Service. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device may provide to us in connection with your use of the Service, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, WiFi information such as SSID, unique device identifier, advertising identifier, location (including geolocation, beacon based location, and GPS location), and requested and referring URLs. 

### 2\. COOKIES

We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, tags, scripts, local shared objects such as HTML5 and Flash (sometimes called "flash cookies"), advertising identifiers (including mobile identifiers such as Apple’s IDFA or Google’s Advertising ID) and similar technology ("Cookies") in connection with your use of the Service, third party websites, and mobile applications. Cookies may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Service, such as your browser type, search preferences, IP address, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session. 

The purposes for which we use Cookies in the Service include: 

Purpose | Explanation  
---|---  
Processes |  Intended to make the Service work in the way you expect. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have already signed up for an account.   
Authentication, Security, and Compliance |  Intended to prevent fraud, protect your data from unauthorized parties, and comply with legal requirements. For example, we use Cookies to determine if you are logged in.   
Preferences |  Intended to remember information about how you prefer the Service to behave and look. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have declined to allow us to send push notifications to your phone.   
Notifications |  Intended to allow or prevent notices of information or options that we think could improve your use of the Service. For example, we use a Cookie that stops us from showing you the signup notification if you have already seen it.   
Advertising |  Intended to make advertising more relevant to users and more valuable to advertisers. For example, we may use Cookies to serve you interest-based ads, such as ads that are displayed to you based on your visits to other websites, or to tell us if you have recently clicked on an ad.   
Analytics |  Intended to allow or prevent notices of information or options that we think could improve your use of the Service. For example, we use a Cookie that stops us from showing you the signup notification if you have already seen it.   
  
You can set some Cookie preferences through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect the functionality of the Service. The method for disabling Cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in your device or browser preferences or security settings. For example, iOS and Android devices each have settings which are designed to limit forms of ad tracking. For flash cookies, you can manage your privacy settings by clicking here. Please note that changing any of these settings does not prevent the display of certain advertisements to you. 

### 3\. THIRD PARTIES

Third parties may receive information about you as follows: 

  1. **Advertisers:** We may allow third parties to use Cookies through the Service to collect the same type of information for the same purposes as we do. In doing so, we adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. Third parties may be able to associate the information they collect with other information they have about you from other sources. We do not necessarily have access to or control over the Cookies they use, but you may be able to opt out of some of their practices by visiting the following links: [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/), [Omniture](https://www.d1.sc.omtrdc.net/optout.html?omniture=1&popup=1&locale=en_US&second=1&second_has_cookie=0) and [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/). Please note that opting out does not prevent the display of all advertisements to you. Additionally, we may share non-personally identifiable information from or about you with third parties, such as location data, advertising identifiers, or a cryptographic hash of a common account identifier (such as an email address) to facilitate the display of targeted advertising. You may be able to limit our sharing of some of this information through your mobile device settings, as described in Section 2 above, or through the Service’s settings. 
  2. **Service Providers:** We may rely on third party providers to support or provide some of the services that are available through the Service, such as email delivery with Mailchimp and analytics tracking with Google Analytics. We may also rely on third party providers to perform certain services for us in connection with your use of the Service, such as communications and hosting services, network security, technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, our own marketing of the Service, and other functions. We may share information from or about you with these third party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests. These third party providers may share information with us that they obtain from or about you in connection with providing their services or completing your requests. Third party providers may also share this information with their subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control. Some of our web pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to you from our third party providers, while preserving the look and feel of the Service. In such cases, please note that the information you provide is being provided to the third party. 
  3. **Aggregate or Anonymous Information:** We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as affiliates that are advertised on AncientFaces and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements. We may also disclose anonymized information about your use on AncientFaces, for example if you engage in uploading photos and biographies on AncientFaces, we may publicly disclose information about the quantity of photos and biographies without providing identifying information about you or otherwise disclosing your participation in the process. 
  4. **Business Transfers:** We may share information from or about you with our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires AncientFaces, or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy. 
  5. **Investigations and Legal Disclosures:** We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure: (a) is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process or law enforcement requests served on us; (b) is helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service; or (c) protects our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. If you flag or otherwise complain to us about content through the Service, we may share the substance of your complaint with the contributor of that content in order to provide an opportunity for the contributor to respond. 
  6. **Links:** The Service may link to third party services, like a business’s URL, or other websites. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on or applicable to all such third party services. 
  7. **Third Party Accounts:** If you sign up for, or log into, AncientFaces using a third party service like Facebook, or link your AncientFaces account to your account with a third party service like Facebook, we may receive information about you from such third party service. If you post content to a third party service through the Service, that third party service will also receive that content, which will be visible to anyone that has access to it through that third party service. 

### 4\. CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

Other users may be able to identify you, or associate you with your account, from your account profile and if you include personal information in the content you post publicly. You can reduce the risk of being personally identified by using the Service pseudonymously, though doing so could detract from the credibility of your contributions to the Service. Please note that the messages you send or receive using the Service are only private to the extent that both you and the person you are communicating with keep them private. For example, if you send a message to another user, that user may choose to publicly post it. Also, we may access and disclose such messages in the course of investigations relating to use of the Service. 

### 5\. DATA RETENTION AND ACCOUNT TERMINATION

You can close your account by [contacting us](https://www.ancientfaces.com/content/contact). We will remove all or a portion of all uploads you have added to AncientFaces and certain public posts from view and/or dissociate them from your account profile, but we may retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law. For example, we may retain information to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service or to comply with legal obligations. Please note that businesses cannot remove their business listings, ratings, or reviews by closing their accounts. 

### 6\. CHILDREN

The Service is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us [here](https://www.ancientfaces.com/content/contact). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. 

### 7\. SECURITY

We use various safeguards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### 8\. CONTACT

You may [contact us online](https://www.ancientfaces.com/content/contact) concerning our Privacy Policy, or write to us at the following address:   
AncientFaces, Attn: Data Privacy Manager  

### 9\. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you and will be located on [https://www.ancientfaces.com/content/privacy](https://www.ancientfaces.com/content/contact). If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Service prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use the Service after those changes become effective, you acknowledge the revised Privacy Policy. 

### 10\. CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you unless you first agree to such disclosure. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed above in Section 8.
